https://www.spiritualitybeyond.com/privacy-policy/

Contact
Who We Are: www.spiritualitybeyond.com, www.mediumvideoseries.com, and www.truthfulpredictions.com
What Personal Data We Collect, And Why We Collect It: We do not collect personal data via our web site.
Media, Comments $ Cookies: We do not allow media uploads or comments on our site, and therefore do not collect any personal data via this method.
Contact Forms:
When you fill out a form on my website the information you have provided may be:
Mailed back to the address entered in the form showing what you filled out.
What has been mailed back is deleted in 3 days…nothing stored.
Embedded Contact From Other Web Sites: We do not embed anything from other web sites.
Analytics: Who We Share Your Data With & How Long We Retain Your Data: We do not retain your data, nor share your data.
What Rights Do You Have Over Your Data? We do not store, share your data.
Where We Send Your Data: We send your data through your filled out form through Gmail, with your email address, your address is saved in a newsletter file, if you sign up for this service, if you chose to unsubscribe, you are taken of the newsletter list immediately, deleted from any future contact from you.
How We Protect Your Data:
Our website data is protected by our web hosting company on a Linux CentOS 7 Apache server.
Our website is protected by a 256-bit Encryption, SHA-2 Security Certificate verified by RapidSSL.
Our website data including any submitted content is backed up in a multi-tiered cloud based system and backup hardrives done by our web provider services.
Contact Information:
Company: Above & Beyond Holistic Services
Address: Mesa, Az 85206
Phone: 1-480-319-5526
Email Address: dyanne@spiritualitybeyond.com
Additional Information: Your security of your personal data is very important to us.
What People Say...
From Gilberto
"It has been about 11 years since I broke up with my ex and remember how hard it was , it was then when somehow I ran into Diane Yellowlight's website .I contacted her and explained the situation to her And ever since then not only all things that she has predicted have been 100% accurate , but I also found her very helpful and given me lots of insight and got hooked cause I have found lots of peace every time I speak to her . I highly recommend her to those need some help putting together tools to better themselves!" ~ Gilberto Heras
From La Jeanne
"Yes, yes and yes...trust, she has experience, kindness, truth, sincerity, she delivers.. If you need to hear it, she may access your guides with a message you need to hear, yet with compassionate tact, deliver it. Don't we all 'need' to hear the truth or we wouldn't ask?. We have read for each other, consoled each other, and over the years she has been what I needed every time. How can I say it as another gifted reader...she is the one I go to!" ~ La Jeanne De Walt
From Karen
"I have known Dyanne Yellowlight since 1996 as she helped me through a very difficult time then. She has helped guide not only me but also my children through choices in our lives. She has been very accurate and honest while guiding me and my children. Dyanne is an excellent source when it comes to seeking guidance, advice and insight." ~ Karen Negrete
From Jennifer
"I am so glad that I found Dyanne. There were things that I wasn't certain about, and she not only cleared things up for me, she eased my mind. She has been working with me since May, 18, 2017. There are many psychics out there. Too many of them take your money and do not help you. They give false information leaving you with no peace. Dyanne Yellowlight IS THE REAL DEAL!!!!!!! She as been reading cards and helping people for 50+ years." ~ Jennifer Swords
From Linda
"Dyanne Yellowlight accurately described the attributes of the man I would marry and she and told me the exact month I would meet him -- that was 21 years ago and we have been married for 19 years. She accurately predicted I would be selected for a big professional promotion and she told me when I would leave that position for other opportunities -- both happened. She has calmed my fears and guided me though medical, family, travel and so many aspects of life." ~ Linda Cinson (Ohio)
From Carla
"I have been utilizing Dyanne for over 7 years now. She is wise, knowledgeable, and compassionate. She is both a good psychic and a good person. The email readings are quick, easy, affordable, and convenient when you need a question answered." ~ Carla Markowski
Latest News & Predictions
Now that we have “Arrived” were we’re at, at the “Peak” Of the “Collapse” of the “Evil” ruling the “Flesh”.. To Co-Create Building the”Heaven” On “Earth” in Flesh…. Are you ready to “Let Go”? Plus “you’ve” walked the road of “Hell” in flesh.. Aren’t “You” ready to give up the “”Struggle”.? Becoming the “Souls” you… More >>>
My Psychic Services
** Web Special **
Email Readings
Clairvoyant Readings
Phone Readings
Video Chat Readings
Monthly Membership
Join My Psychic Circle
Your Name
Email Address
Subscribe
Copyright©2003-2020. All Rights Reserved. The content of this psychic reading, online medium, and clairvoyant site focusing on the supernatural, holistic, and esoteric is owned exclusively by Above and Beyond Holistic Services featuring the psychic and clairvoyant visions of Dyanne Yellowlight.
Privacy Policy.
For Entertainment Purposes Only.
In these troubled times, don't let fate get the best of you.
Use my intuitive gift to help guide you through your life choices...
Call Today (480) 319-5526
Email Readings | Phone Readings | Video Readings | Monthly Membership
Thank you for visiting my website! Get a real Psychic Reading & Clairvoyant Visions today and have me see into your future!
Psychic Readings, Medium & Clairvoyant Site Design by Reliable Web Designs.
